<resources>
    <!-- main page -->
    <string name="app_name">Go Travel Scotland</string>
    <string name="main_paragraph">BEGIN YOUR JOURNEY ON THE LOCH NESS TOUR</string>
    <string name="language_select">Select language then press start</string>
    <string name="start">start</string>

    <!-- instructions fragments-->
    <string name="instructions_msg_one">Plug in your headphones</string>
    <string name="instructions_msg_two">Sit comfortably</string>
    <string name="instructions_msg_three">Begin your very own tour experience</string>
    <string name="lets_begin">Lets Begin</string>

    <string name="the_departure">The Departure</string>

    <!-- homepage -->
    <string name="homepage_title">What would you like to do?</string>
    <string name="homepage_para">You have the power to create the experience you want</string>
    <string name="video_tour_button_text">video tour</string>
    <string name="children_button_text">children</string>
    <string name="extras_button_text">extras</string>

    <!-- tour home page -->
    <string name="tour_home_page_title">Lets Start!</string>
    <string name="tour_home_page_para">Select the section that corresponds to where you are
    on your journey. To have the best experience we do not recommend skipping ahead!</string>
    <string name="start_here_button_text">start here</string>
    <string name="towards_loch_ness_button_text">towards loch ness</string>
    <string name="highlands_and_lochs_button_text">Highlands and Lochs</string>
    <string name="heros_and_freedom_button_text">Hero\'s and Freedom</string>

    <!-- extra page -->
    <string name="extra_page_title">Relax</string>
    <string name="extra_page_para">We have a selection of onboard entertainment options you
    can choose from. Please note wifi is restricted to certain parts of our journey due to
    network coverage in the Scottish highlands</string>
    <string name="extra_button_text">extra</string>
    <string name="whatson_button_text">what\'s on</string>
    <string name="shop_button_text">shop</string>
    <string name="web_button_text">web</string>

    <!-- whats on page -->
    <string name="whatson_page_title">What\'s On</string>

    <!-- children page -->
    <string name="children_page_title">Childrens Area</string>
    <string name="children_page_para">We have lots of fun things for you to enjoy on your
    adventure around Scotland!</string>
    <string name="children_page_ep1_title">1. Nessie goes to School</string>
    <string name="children_page_ep1_para">Join nessie as he goes to school for the first
    time. School can be a scary place for the first time but luckily, he\'s got a massive
    cock so he is full of confedence</string>

    <!-- tour Ad slide -->
    <string name="start_next_tour_button_text">Start Next Tour</string>

    <string name="place_holder_para">This is some text that has been typed up to give an example
    of the type of stuff that will be going into this app. It has become very complicated to so this
    and I have lost the desire to ever become an app developer so Android can suck my balls.</string>

    <!-- Terms and Conditions -->
    <string name="terms_and_conditions_title">Terms and Conditions</string>
    <string name="terms_and_conditions">   It is your responsibility to check the condition of all
        portable equipment at the time of issue. Faults that are discovered or damage incurred while
        you are in possession of the equipment must be reported to the driver as soon as possible.
        If equipment becomes unusable it should be returned to the driver.All equipment is logged
        and monitored to ensure that we can trace the users in the event of damage or loss.You must
        not use the equipment in a way that breaches any Go Travel Scotland regulations or policy or
        that brings Go Travel Scotland into disrepute.Users are only permitted to use the tablet to
        follow the tour and make use of the free WiFiand ‘What’s On’ section to research things to
        do in Scotland.You may not record or duplicate any images, videos or text from our tour app.
        Equipment is to stay on the coach at all times.  Users may not take the equipment off the
        coach at any destinations or stops.  Equipment is monitored with GPS tracking and users
        maybe prosecuted for theft for taking equipment.Equipment must be returned as you leave
        the coach at the end of a tour.Each item should be returned in the condition in which it was
        borrowed. Do not change anysettings.All equipment must be returned directly to the driver.
        Customers who fail to comply with these conditions could face prosecution for damage or
        vandalism.

        By using Go Travel Scotland equipment you are agreeing to the terms and conditions of
        booking listed above and you accept that you are fully responsible for any and all damage or
        loss to the equipment in your booking.</string>


    <!-- ======= Tours ====== -->
    <!-- start here slides -->
    <!-- edinburgh -->
    <string name="edinburgh_title">Edinburgh</string>
    <string name="edinburgh_para">We depart the city on Edinburgh and head towards the Highlands and
    Pitlochry. There are many sights and interesting facts to learn along the way. Once you\'ve
    watched the videos check out the extra facts on some of the topics covered</string>

    <!-- departure slide -->
    <string name="departure_start_here_title">Departure</string>
    <string name="departure_start_here_para">The first part of our video tour guide will follow the route we take from
        Edinburgh to Pitlochry. These videos are designed to give you a taste of Scottish history
        before we reach our destinations.</string>

    <string name="scottish_world_heritage_title">Scottish World Heritage</string>
    <string name="scottish_world_heritage_para">We will shortly be crossing over the Firth of Forth.</string>

    <string name="kingdom_of_fife_title">Kingdom of Fife</string>
    <string name="the_kingdome_of_fife_para">Once we have crossed over the Firth of Forth we are now entering The Kingdom of Fife.
\“Beggars mantel fringed with Gold\”</string>

    <string name="loch_leven_title">Loch Leven</string>
    <string name="loch_leven_para">The wonderful Loch Leven</string>

    <string name="perth_title">Perth</string>
    <stirng name="perth_para">The ancient capital of the Highlands</stirng>

    <string name="dunkeld_title">Dunkeld</string>
    <stirng name="dunkeld_para">Watch this video once we have left Perth</stirng>

    <string name="pitlochry_title">Pitlochry</string>
    <string name="pitlochry_para">The town of Pitlochry is our first stop of today.
Please speak to the driver about tickets for Cruise Loch Ness.</string>

    <string name="departure_towards_loch_ness_title">Leaving Pitlochry</string>
    <string name="departure_towards_loch_ness_para">Make sure you have booked and paid for your
        tickets for Cruise Loch Ness! We now leave Pitlochry and travel towards Loch Ness.
</string>



    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
</resources>
